beamcablesystem.in 2009-02-11

# 

| 

|  | **What This Privacy Policy Covers**  
---|---  
   
| **Information Collection and Use**  
---|---  
  |  **General**  
|   |   
---|---|---  
  |  |   |  | 

The Company collects personal information when you register with the Company , when you use the Company products or services, when you visit   
  
---|---|---  
  |   | 

the Company pages or the pages of certain partners of the Company. The Company may combine information about you that we have with  
  
  |   | 

information we obtain from business partners or other companies. The Company shall have the right pass on the same to its business   
  
  |   | associates, franchisees without referring the same to you.   
  |  | When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal   
  |   | interests. Once you register with the Company and sign in to our services, you become our valued customer.   
|  | The Company collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use   
  |   | of products and services that we offer.   
  |  | The Company can use information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for   
  |   | products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.   
   
|   |   
   
| **Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
---|---  
|   |   
---|---|---  
  |  |   |  | 

The Company may share personal information about you with other people under the following circumstances:   
  
---|---|---  
  |   |  | 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with the Company under confidentiality agreements. These companies   
  
  |   |   | 

may use your personal information to help the Company communicate with you about offers from the Company and our marketing partners.   
  
  |   |  | We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud,  
  |   |   | situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Company's terms of use, or as otherwise required by   
  |   |   | law.  
|   |  | We transfer information about you if the Company is acquired by or merged with another company under a diffferent management. In this event,   
  |   |   | the Company will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.   
  |  | The Company plans to display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may   
  |   |  assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular  
  |   | geographic area.   
  |   |  | The Company will not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting   
  |   |   | with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used   
  |   |   | to display the ad. .   
  |  | The Company works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and service providers in many different industries and categories of business.   
  |  | We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Company's service, such as service announcements, administrative   
  |   | messages and the Company's Newsletter, that are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them..  
   
|   |   
   
| **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
---|---  
  
The Company may update this policy and display the same in their website without notice to you and such posting will be deemed to have been read by you.
